cinematography.com 2015-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Cinematography.com

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognized by our web servers.

We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

**Security Measures**

We make access to privacy-sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

We will provide individually-identifiable information about consumers to third parties only if we are compelled to do so by order of a duly-empowered governmental authority, we have the express permission of the consumer, or it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services.

**Privacy and Our Business Partners**

When we make our technology or services available to business partners, we will not share with them any more consumer information than is necessary and we will make every reasonable effort to assure, by contract or otherwise, that they use our technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Email Addresses**

Cinematography.com does not sell its mailing list and will not share individual email address with third-parties. 

  1.  
  2. [Privacy Policy](http://www.cinematography.com/index.php?app=core&module=global&section=privacy)
  3. [Forum Guidelines](http://www.cinematography.com/index.php?app=forums&module=extras&section=boardrules) ·
